ANTONY CHACKO

FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPER



CONTACT

Address: Bengaluru, Karnataka

Phone: 7012590855

Email: antony101tony@gmail.com





PROJECTS

Acko Clone (

clone of Acko, where you can insure your vehicle easily online.

Tech Stack: ReactJs | CSS | Javascript | Node | MongoDB | Mongoose | Express

Areas of responsibility:

- Horizontal sliders to select insurance amount.
- Implemented Frontend for insurance plan selection.
- Implemented backend database and REST Apis for the insurance amount selection.

A collaborative project built by a team of 6 including 2 UI designers, executed in 6 days.

Ecogenic (7)

Eco Genic is a project which focuses on helping people attain a sustainable lifestyle.

Tech Stack: ReactJs | CSS | Javascript | Node | MongoDB | Mongoose | Express

Areas of responsibility:

- Created the Carbon footprint bar diagram page and schemes selection page.
- Created the Topics interested page.

A collaborative project built by a team of 5 including 1 UI designer, executed in 6 days.

AWARDS AND RECOGNITIONS

Committee Head

Nakshatra National Inter-College Fest February, 2018

Best Project

Our Ecogenic Project got selected as one of 3 best projects in masai school.

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

An ambitious and self-motivated Full Stack Web Developer with considerable technical skills. Possesses self-discipline and the ability to work with minimum supervision. Able to play a key role in website development to ensure maximum accessibility, user experience, and usability.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Full-Stack Web Developer

Tracxn Technologies, Bangalore | Feb 2022 - Present

- Development of both FrontEnd and Backend for the various features offered by the company website.
- Ananlyzed, Designed and Developed 20+ requirements from product team.
- Debugged and fixed 30+ bugs.
- Refactured and optimised code for a major feature.

Quality Controller

ENCONPASS, Bangalore | Jan 2019 - March 2021

- Inspecting the Quality of Industrial Automation Control panels and preparing reports.
- Performing in-house Control Panel testing and assisting the customers with it.

EDUCATION

Masai School, Bangalore

Full-Stack Development (Online) | June 2021 - Jan 2022

Capital University Jharkhand

B.Tech Electronics and Instrumentation Engineering May 2013- June 2018 | 64%

Higher Secondary Education

St. Geroge Higher Secondary School May 2011- March 2013 | 84%

High School Education

St.Geroge Higher Secondary School March 2013 | 86%

SKILLS AND FRAMEWORKS

React Js | NodeJs | MongoDb | ExpressJS | HTML | CSS

SOFT SKILLS

Team Collaboration | Remote Work | Problem Solving

INTERESTS

Have a home music studio and a YouTube channel that feature Cover songs and Vlogs.